Let's do a training camp!
A training camp?
It hit me after that quiz show the other day.
We don't have nearly enough teamwork!
Hence, the training camp!
Training Camp!!
I don't want to go out in this heat.
This is part of work too!
We'll train our singing and dancing
and learn more about each other!
And we can top it off
by making a casual video!
We'll have a barbecue too!
I'm in! I wanna go!
I like your enthusiasm!
You too, Sena!
Alright.
What about you, Lulu-chan?
Umm...
Let's go! I wanna talk to you more!
Okay, then!
That settles it! We're doing a training camp!
Yeah!
Bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae
Bae, bae, bae
Bubee, bubee
Bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae
Ooh, ooh, ooh
You're my little buddy
Magical Sisters LuluttoLilly
Hey, bubee love
Bubee, bubee, bubee love
Magical Sisters LuluttoLilly
My heart is racing like crazy
And right before my eyes
Are the colors of a brand new world
Whoa
Stay with me today
We'll walk hand in hand
Dreaming of the place where we can become light
I can hear the magic
I wanna sing with you
Let's sing together
You're a bright shining star
My bubee, bubee, bubee love
We can be shining stars
Forever and ever
That's our secret magic
My bubee, bubee, bubee love
Ooh, ooh, ooh
You're my little buddy
Hey, bubee love
Bubee, bubee, bubee love
Bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae
Bae, bae, bae
Bubee, bubee
B-U-B-E-E, bubee
Bubee love
Nothing Screams Summer Like a Training Camp
What's the matter?
Azuki...
How do I tell Mom and Dad
that I'm staying over somewhere?
Good question...
I need an excuse...
Should I just tell them the truth?
You can't! Your magic has to stay a secret!
Why not just tell them you're helping a friend?
Because I don't have any friends.
I'm your friend!
Fuu
Uguisu, how do I give this to her?
How about normally?
How is "normally"? Tell me!
What?
First, think of the training camp.
Right, the training camp!
I need an excuse...
I know!
Litto!
Lililula, palilula!
Make my training camp work out just fine!
What's that supposed to do?
I'm counting on you!
Alright! Back to our strategy meeting
on how to give big sis my present!
Huh?! No way, I'm sleepy!
Are you ready?
Yeah, I'm set.
Good.
Oh, Fuu!
G'morning...
Sorry this is sudden!
Mom and I have to head out soon.
Huh?
Our shop and Mari-chan's are taking part
in a market a bit far away from here.
Far away? Where is it?
Hm, where was it again?
I think it was... west, right?
West.
Check Lock
Warning Mode
Notice
I'm here to pick you up!
Rui, Fuu, I'm borrowing your parents, okay?
We're on our way out!
So yeah, it's west.
We'll be back the night after tomorrow.
Huh? The night after tomorrow?
Umm, I also have plans to go... out...
Oh, you too, big sis?
You too?
Don't forget to lock the doors!
It's west... right? West!
Magic is awesome!
Good job.
I'm all ready to go!
Fuu?
Um, so...
Here!
I saw these the other day
and thought they were cute,
so I'm letting you have one!
Huh?
It was a set of two.
Thank you!
I love the scent.
I'll put it to good use!
Okay!
FURYU
CONFECTIONERY
I gave it to her!
Lililula, palilula!
Pam pam power!
I'm just as cute as ever!
We're adorable!
There she is.
Hey, over here!
I'm here!
Good morning!
You look happy.
You must be really excited for this.
Which one will you pick?
Aww, again?!
Your turn, Lulu.
Lulu-chan!
O-Okay!
Sorry...
I'm out!
Aw, man!
My turn.
Sorry, I'm all out!
You're too reactive.
This'll be it!
Hold on, now.
You're always hanging around us, huh?
But you do know we're on a train, right?
Uh, you want some?
Really...?
It's the sea!
Wow!
It's better than I expected!
This cottage... is very big!
This place is so spacious!
It's pretty on the inside too.
I'm gonna go explore!
This will make a good game
of hide and seek!
This'll do.
We can use this for practice.
I'm back!
I can't believe you were able
to rent a fancy place like this.
What is it...?
You won't believe it. It was super cheap!
Ain't that right, Prez?
It has a private beach, and it's less than half
the price of the surrounding properties.
It sounds like it went up for sale at first,
but no one bought it, so they started renting it out instead.
Certainly a bargain for us.
I'm lodging somewhere else,
so you girls take care of this place.
Don't cause any trouble for your neighbors.
We won't!
Well...
Not like they have any neighbors.
So, um... how do we start our training camp?
We go on an adventure, right?
Shouldn't we decide on our rooms?
That can wait. First order of business...
We swim!
Why do we have swimsuits?
She said she brought them
from the agency.
Can we really go swim?
S-She's right! We're here to practice.
Seriously? Summer means sea,
and we've got our own private beach!
It's only the natural thing to do!
Let's swim.
Really?
Yay!
Slow down!
You too, Lulu!
What?!
ONCE MORE
SENA
TOKO
LILLY
LULU
The agency's gotten a lot livelier lately.
To think it was just us two originally.
Well, the president was there too.
Oh, yeah.
But still, we're pretty lucky
those girls joined us.
Do you think we're on track...
to dominate showbiz?
Who knows.
Steady, steady...
Next, lip rolls.
Again, but like you're sighing.
Next, humming.
Again!
Look at her go.
How can she dance so well
after all that playing?
It's because she's serious.
In Toko's eyes, the most important part
to being an idol is giving your all in everything.
Toko-san is amazing.
Lulu and Lilly, your task for today
is to memorize the dance I just did.
Huh?!
W-Will we be able to?
You have to! Sena, any advice for them?
Do it 300 times and you'll have it memorized.
Three hundred?!
And no dinner until you've got it down!
Being an idol is tough work!
L-Let's do our best, Lilly-san!
Can you bring this to the others?
Okay!
What the?
I can't do it!
I can't move...
Keep doing it and you'll get the hang of it.
Thank you...
Oh, Kabappy!
Let's take a break.
Yeah.
Um...
Oh, right. How long have you and Toko-san been idols?
Since spring last year.
Toko brought it up out of nowhere.
Really?
We went through a lot,
but none of it worked out.
Until you two came along.
Huh?
Toko's gone on about it, like,
"now that they're here, I might achieve my dream."
Her dream?
Yeah.
She wants to succeed as an idol
and shock everyone.
That's her dream.
And she made a whole company
just to make it come true.
She's always been bold like that.
Are you like, super close?
We're just normal friends.
Show me some old pictures!
No way. It's embarrassing.
C'mon, show me!
I brought drinks.
Thanks.
I wanna see!
Also, I want to see those pictures too...
Really?
Show me!
Someone sounds perky.
Alright, break time's over!
Let's go over that last part!
It should be live now... I think?
What do we talk about on the livestream?
I'm so nervous!
Oh, we have some viewers!
Good evening! We're Production Once More!
This is our first video!
Everyone, say hello!
Hey, I'm Sena.
Good evening, I'm Lilly!
I'm L-Lu-Lulu!
"Lululu"...?
You're trying too hard.
No, I'm not!
And finally, I'm Toko!
Oh! We have a comment!
"Where are you?"
We're at a cottage doing
a training camp!
Yeah!
Y-Yeah!
So, um, do we have any topics?
Topics, topics...
Do you have one, Lulu-chan?
A topic?
Yeah!
We all talked so much
before we started recording...
Alright!
Oh, we're getting a lot of new viewers!
Good evening!
Another comment!
"I saw the Hell's Quiz!"...
Wow, looks like a lot of people tuned into that!
"I'm such a big fan!"
Thank you!
Th-Thank you very much!
If we get more fans like we planned,
then we've got this.
"I love you, Lilly-chan!"
Look! One of them says they love Lilly-san!
Thank you!
"I'm your fan, Lilly-chan!"
I love you, Lilly-chan!!
I'm your fan, Lilly-chan!
I'm supporting you, Lulu-chan!
I love you, Lilly-chan!!
I'm your fan, Lilly-chan!
I'm supporting you, Lulu-chan!
I love you, Lilly-chan!!
I'm your fan, Lilly-chan!
I'm supporting you, Lulu-chan!
I love you, Lilly-chan!!
I'm your fan, Lilly-chan!
I'm supporting you, Lulu-chan!
I love you, Lilly-chan!!
I'm your fan, Lilly-chan!
I'm supporting you, Lulu-chan!
I love you, Lilly-chan!!
I'm your fan, Lilly-chan!
I'm supporting you, Lulu-chan!
I love you, Lilly-chan!!
I'm your fan, Lilly-chan!
I'm supporting you, Lulu-chan!
What are your image colors?
I love you, Lilly-chan!!
I'm your fan, Lilly-chan!
I'm supporting you, Lulu-chan!
What are your image colors?
I love you, Lilly-chan!!
I'm your fan, Lilly-chan!
I'm supporting you, Lulu-chan!
What are your image colors?
I love you, Lilly-chan!!
I'm your fan, Lilly-chan!
I'm supporting you, Lulu-chan!
What are your image colors?
I love you, Lilly-chan!!
I'm your fan, Lilly-chan!
I'm supporting you, Lulu-chan!
What are your image colors?
I love you, Lilly-chan!!
I'm your fan, Lilly-chan!
I'm supporting you, Lulu-chan!
What are your image colors?
I'm your fan, Lilly-chan!
I'm supporting you, Lulu-chan!
What are your image colors?
When is your next concert?
I'm your fan, Lilly-chan!
I'm supporting you, Lulu-chan!
What are your image colors?
When is your next concert?
Whoa, we're getting a lot!
That's great! If anyone has questions,
send them our way!
Lilly-chan's so cute when she's flustered, wah!
Wait, slow down!
Who's your oshi?
Mine is Lilly-chan!
What idol is your god?
I can't keep up with this!
Lilly-chan, what do you do
on your days off??
Wait! Slow down a little please!
Hold on!
"You're all amazing!"
Oh, more comments! Yay!
That was a lot, but it was so fun!
We hit 3,000 viewers.
We just can't keep up with that.
It took me by surprise.
We didn't get nearly as much of a reception
when it was just the two of us.
So I guess I have you two to thank for that.
Please, you don't!
I mean it, seriously!
Thank you for joining our agency.
But you won't get the best of me!
We'll whip you into shape again tomorrow!
But for now, we sleep!
Whip us into shape?!
Oh boy, she's all pumped up.
Please be gentle on us.
Gotta pee...
Couldn't you have gone alone...?
I can't help it, it's scary...
Where are you from?
Where are you going?
Wait up! Hey!
Alarm
Stop
Azuki?
Did she go to Uguisu?
Good morning!
Good morning! Did you sleep good?
Yes.
Morning.
All that's left is Lilly.
I sorta figured she wasn't a morning gal.
Same.
I'll go wake her.
Lilly-san!
Good morning!
It's time to wake up!
She's gone...
Azuki and Uguisu too...
She's gone?
Yes. I checked the other rooms too,
but couldn't find her anywhere.
Lilly! Where are you?
Lilly!
Did she go outside?
Maybe to the beach?
What the...?
Toko-san?
The door won't open, but it's not locked...
Huh? I think you're just half-asleep.
I'm serious! Try it yourself.
It won't budge.
We could try the other exits.
This won't budge either.
Even the windows are stuck?
Dang it.
What's going on?
T-Toko-san...
I'll call Prez.
What is it?
Prez, it's an emergency.
Lilly's gone missing.
Are you sure she's not just on a walk?
She can't be!
We're stuck inside too.
I can't... you... You there?
I told you!
Hey, turn off the TV.
Huh?
Laughing...?
Look, I can't hear you over
all that weird noise.
What are you talking about? The TV's not on.
Anyways, we need you to—
Huh? Uh, um... Toko?
Prez? Prez?!
President
Call Ended
What's wrong?
President
Calling...
No connection.
I lost signal.
Lilly?
Lilly?!
What the heck?!
What's happening?
Courage is in two worlds, yeah, together now
(Proof!)
It's what binds us together
Everyone smiles at the beautiful girls
(My dream!)
I just wanna know what the future holds
(Alone!)
Even if the stars in a moonless sky
Still twinkle
(No magic!)
Even if the clouds in a sunless sky
Still drift
I feel so lonely
(I was always right beside you)
I'm searching for you
I'll frame a photo of us two and hang it up
Let's set things the way we want, the way we will, the way they are
Take our chemistry, plus+, minus-, multiplied×, divided÷ by...
I love it every way
Calling me, calling you
(And you)
I want to walk up the stairs of the future with you
Lucky lucky shiny, our beating hearts dreamin' away
If there's clear skies tomorrow, everything will be okay
Maybe I'm a bit sad and weak
(But I'm happy!)
But when I'm with you I feel safe
There's no such thing as wasted time
Let's wait until the rain stops
Check it out, look up at the sky
Courage is in two worlds, yeah, together now
(Proof!)
That's what binds us together
Everyone smiles at the beautiful girls
What kind of future will the spotlight shine on?
Summer Daydream